迈克 · 诺斯: 让我们应用我们新学到的三阶段转换方法
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's apply our newly
learned three phase approach to converting
将一段 JavaScript 代码转换成打字稿。
a piece of JavaScript
code into TypeScript.
所以我为你们写了这样一个例子。
So I've written such an example for you.
在通讯录下的“挑战”文件夹里。
It's in the challenges
folder under address book.
这里有一个输入错误，不是 index.ts，而是 index.js。
And there's a little typo here
that's not index.ts, it is index.js.
唯一的文件在地址簿文件夹，所以希望我们能找出来。
The only file in the address book folder,
so hopefully we'll figure that out.
Mike North: 为了理解，让我们来看看这段代码
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's take a look at this
piece of code in order to understand
它的各个方面
the various aspects of it and
我们可能需要考虑类型信息。
where we might need to think
about type information.
我们有一个叫做 addressbook 的类
So we've got a class here
called AdressBook and
我们一会儿再深入讨论。
we'll dig into that in a moment.
我们有一个函数叫格式化日期,
We've got a function here
called the formatDate,
和 getVcardText。
getFullName, and getVcardText.
如果你从未听说过 Vcard，你可以创建一个 Vcard 文件,
If you've never heard of Vcard,
you can create a Vcard file,
只是一个文本文件，里面有联系方式。
it's just a text file with
contact information in it.
你可以把这个安装到你的联系人应用程序或者其他什么地方。
And you can install this in
your contacts app or something.
在 AddressBook 类中，我们有一个看起来像是用于联系人的数组。
In the AddressBook class, we have an array
that looks like it's for contacts.
一个添加联系人的方法，然后按名称查找联系人。
A method to add contact, and
then find a contact by name.
因此，三个步骤中的第一步让我们重新命名
So, the first of the three
steps has us renaming
从 JS 到 TS，并设置打字稿编译器
this file from JS to TS, and
setting the TypeScript compiler
直到我们能让事情顺利进行。
in a very loose mode until
we can get things passing.
第0步是确保测试在我们完成之前和之后都通过。
Step 0 is making sure that the tests
pass before and after we are done.
迈克 · 诺斯: 好的，14个测试中有14个通过了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Okay,
14 out of 14 tests passed.
看来我们可以开始了。
So, looks like we are good to get started.